Baby, turn around.
Turn around.
Slow down.
The baby is going to get carsick.
You like this pendant so much,
I'll make you another one.
No.
I only like this one.
Go cook.
I want
braised beef
and tomatoes with eggs.
You've been in the UK for so long,
but you still prefer Chinese food.
You're such a foodie.
Wait a moment.
It'll be ready soon.
What do you think
we should name our baby?
How about
Wang Yile?
What do you think?
Hmm.
Yile.
Halt!
Mr. Lin,
should I look into
the horse incident?
The equestrian club said it was an accident
and they apologized and compensated.
Forget it.
Guan Lu,
am I leaning on you too much?
It's okay.
I've arrived.
Today,
thank you.
I should be thanking you
for spending time with me today.
Why don't you
come up for a while?
It's not
convenient, right?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just hungry.
Let's grab something to eat together.
Okay.
Come in.
Don't you usually
live with your parents?
Oh,
I prefer
living on my own.
What about you?
Do you live with your parents?
My parents
are no longer with us.
I don't have any other family now.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Let's order takeout.
We're home.
Why do we order takeout?
I'll cook.
You don't usually cook?
I...
I don't know how to cook.
So there's nothing in the fridge.
It's okay.
Noodles are fine.
Did you become independent very early?
My parents passed away early.
I had no choice but to fend for myself.
So
you've been
taking care of yourself all along?
Yes.
I'm used to it.
Okay.
Go get a bowl.
No bowl.
I...
I don't cook.
why do I need a bowl?
What?
Is he okay?
You went to his house?
You go check it out.
See if there's
something fishy going on.
You're not the first woman
to try to climb into my son's bed,
and you won't be the last.
Genius.
Eat.
I'm curious about
what kind of person
you are.
You are experienced and calm when playing billiards.
You are charming when attending a wine party.
You are mature and capable when being a lawyer.
You are gentle and quiet when cooking.
And you saved me without hesitation today.
I can't tell
which one is the real you.
No matter which one,
it's me, isn't it?
Yes.
Anyway,
thank you.
I'm very moved.
If it were you today,
you would save me, too.
You have so much confidence in me.
Wouldn't you save me?
Take a guess.
Stop teasing me.
The noodles are getting cold. Eat up.
Delicious.
Remember
to change your dressing tomorrow.
Oh,
is your
proposal still valid?
What proposal?
The one
about becoming partners.
Making me Mrs. Lin?
Yes.
I'll give you the title of Mrs. Lin,
and you help me take full control.
Are you serious?
You are serious.
Of course, I am.
But we need to set some ground rules.
Go ahead.
First,
we can't force each other
to do anything we don't want to do.
Fair enough.
Second,
during our partnership,
we must be honest with each other.
Any issues should be communicated openly.
There can't be
any deceitful behavior.
Agreed.
Third,
I won't divide your premarital property,
but after marriage,
I will.
I help you achieve a goal,
and you give me shares of Lin Group
as a reward.
That's all?
For now.
Then I have something to say.
If you want to be Mrs. Lin,
you have to get my mom's approval.
Okay.
I'm mentally prepared.
In a couple of days,
you'll have a good chance to make an impression.
What?
My mom's birthday.
But whether you can pass or not
depends on yourself.
Okay.
Pleasure to cooperate.
Looking forward to your performance tomorrow night.
Happy birthday, Mr. Wen.
Thank you.
Mom.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Sorry
I'm late.
Happy birthday.
Let me introduce,
this is
Guan Li, Guan Li'an.
She is also
my girlfriend.
Mr. Wen,
happy birthday.
Tiantian,
the gift for you
has been sent to your room.
It's the sculpture
you like the most.
You are welcome, Ms. Guan.
Jiming,
you should have
told me you're
bringing a colleague.
I just wanted to give you a surprise.
I'll leave you to it.
I'll go
say hello to Mr. Liu.
Director Liu.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Let me introduce.
This is our newly appointed General Counsel,
Ms. Guan.
Ms. Guan,
I've heard so much about you.
Liu Yaping.
Nice to meet you.
Since I got here,
I've been asking around
about this stunning beauty
who's been the talk of the town.
I've never seen her before.
I learned that
she is Guan Lv,
a rising star in Lin Group.
I also heard that
she graduated from
LSE, the sixth-ranked
university in the world
in law.
She is young, promising,
and brilliant.
Chairman Liu, you flatter me.
I'm just serving the group.
Chairman Liu
You need to change your habit of asking personal questions.
Guan Yu is my girlfriend.
If she is scared away,
you have to compensate me.
If I remember correctly,
isn't your girlfriend
Yaru?
Director Liu
I think you have misunderstood.
Jiming
has always regarded Miss Liu
as his sister.
Is that so?
Everyone
Today is my mother's birthday.
Have a good time.
To Mr. Wen.
Cheers.
Mr. Liu.
Good teamwork.
Mom.
Mr. Wen,
Guan Law Firm
is really shining tonight.
Here,
I'll toast to you.
Congratulations.
You've made
such a rapid progress.
Ms. Liu,
I'm not much of a drinker.
I'll take your toast as a compliment.
But there's something
I'm particularly curious about.
Please don't take offense.
I
have a close friend
who studied abroad in the UK
a few years ago.
She was about
the same time as you.
She told me
there was a
Chinese Students Association
that was very active.
The president's last name was Dai.
You're so excellent.
Do you know this president?
The circle of international students
is not big.
President Dai?
Oh,
you should be talking about David.
I'm not very familiar with him,
but I've heard of him.
I heard that
he immigrated to the UK
after graduation.
Look at me,
I'm drunk,
so my memory is not that good.
I got it wrong.
The president
is not surnamed Dai,
but Li.
His surname is Li.
But his English name
is David.
Really?
Yeah.
I was more focused on
studying and internship during those years.
I seldom went to
the gatherings.
But I shouldn't have got his name wrong.
Miss Liu,
if your friend has any problems
in the UK,
feel free to ask me for help.
Yaru,
Lawyer Guan has promised to help your friend,
why don't you toast to her?
Yes, Auntie.
Lawyer Guan,
then this toast,
I sincerely offer to you.
I'll drink first.
But there's one thing,
I can't drink hard liquor.
I'll try my best to block it for you,
but there will be some I can't block,
then it's up to you.
Good things come in pairs.
This second cup
is to let bygones be bygones.
If you don't drink it,
that means you don't forgive me.
Excuse me.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Don't go.
There's a third glass.
Enough.
That's enough.
Ah.
Auntie Wen.
Remember.
No alcohol during the recovery period.
Otherwise, you may suffer from palpitations,
nausea,
and cognitive impairment.
I see.
Thank you, doctor.
Tian.
Jiming.
Jiming, don't go.
Don't leave me.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Ah!